

- aaqiljayah@gmail.com
- Malaysia
- 011-3992 4778
- % aaqiljayah.github.io

Links

in linkedin.com/aaqiljayah

Languages

English

Native proficiency

Sinhalese

Professional working proficiency

Malay

Elementary proficiency

Japanese

Elementary proficiency

Certifications

- AWS Cloud Essentials for Business Leaders
- CCNA: Introduction to Networks by Cisco
- Content Creation: Strategy and Tools by LinkedIn
- Public Speaking Foundations by LinkedIn

Assets

Core Competencies

- Leadership
- Responsible
- Critical thinking
- Teamwork
- Problem Solving

Interests

Community Involvement Learning Languages

Sports

Videography

Photography

Aaqil Jayah

Student

Reliable student currently studying Cyber Security seeks an internship opportunity to expand skills and gain valuable real-world experience. Considered hardworking, punctual and driven. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals.

Education

BSc (Hons) In Computer Science (Cyber Security)

Since November 2022

Asia Pacific University of Innovation & Technology Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Certificate in Information Technology and Cyber Security Law

From May 2021 to July 2021 National Institute of Business Management Colombo, Sri Lanka

Attended School

From September 2009 to May 2021 Lyceum International School - Wattala Sri Lanka

- IGCSE O/L's 3B (Computer Science, Physics, English Literature), 4C (Mathematics, English Language, Biology and Chemistry).
- IGCSE A/L's 1A (Computer Science), 2B (Mathematics, Physics)

Experience

APU Sri Lankan Community - President

Since December 2023

Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

APU Sri Lankan Community - Vice President

From June 2023 to December 2023

Asia Pacific University of Technology and Innovation Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Freelance Swimming Instructor

Since July 2023 Superprof Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Crew Member

From December 2021 to January 2022 Domino's Pizza Ragama, Sri Lanka

Senior Prefect Application Experience

September 2019 Canon Image Square Colombo, Sri Lanka

Skills

Programming and Operating System Proficiency

Python, C#, Java, R, SQL, HTML, CSS, Linux, Git.

Software Proficiency

Notion, Cisco Packet Tracer, Adobe Premier Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Microsoft Office, WordPress, Github, Canva, Figma.

Personal Achievements

Leadership and Achievements in Education and Sports

- Demonstrated leadership and responsibility as a Junior and Senior Prefect at Lyceum Wattala.
- Showcased exceptional sportsmanship and team leadership skills as the Overall Vice Captain for Football.
- Received the Sports Colours Award at Lyceum Wattala for outstanding achievements in Karate and Football.
- Participated in competitive swimming and athletics, representing Lyceum Wattala in various competitions.
- Represented Lyceum Wattala in multiple events and held positions in the General Knowledge Club and IT Society committee.
- Currently, an active member of the Naga Takraw Club, engaging in the sport of "Sepak Takraw." Proudly represented the Sri Lankan National Team at the King's Cup Sepak Takraw World Championship in Bangkok, Thailand in 2022.